- id: ckw-l10-2559
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コントロール
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2560
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ウイルス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2581
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - サイズ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2588
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - マーク
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2612
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ナンバー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2617
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パワー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2636
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - シーン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2640
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アドバイス
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2643
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ショック
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2648
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アクセス
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2661
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - マイ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2674
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ブルー
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2685
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ラジオ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2701
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - タイトル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l10-2730
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ユーザー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
